officetimeline.com 2017-06-06

# Office Timeline: Privacy Policy

###  We respect the privacy of our customers, partners, employees, job applicants, and other visitors to our websites who may provide personal information. We recognize the need for appropriate protections and management of personal information that you provide to us. Our policy is pretty simple, we do not share your personal information with anyone without your permission. 

###  Credit Card Transactions 

Office Timeline only collects personal information when you contact us or provide feedback and only uses the information collected to provide those services for you. If you choose to make a purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and email address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. Credit card information is collected in its entirety by our merchant, [Stripe](http://www.stripe.com/). Your credit card information and transaction is not handled or stored in any shape or form by Office Timeline. Please note that some information may be stored by Stripe for compliance purposes. 

###  Third Parties 

Any personal information provided will not be traded, rented, sold or otherwise shared with anyone outside of Office Timeline or used for reasons beyond those contemplated in this statement. From time to time, we may engage third parties to process your information on our behalf. However, none of Office Timeline affiliates (such as our credit card company) have permission to retain, share, store or use personal information for any reason other than providing the requested service. 

###  Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure and improper use of your information, we have established appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect the information we collect in accordance with our privacy policy. 

###  Changes to This Statement 

Office Timeline will update this Statement periodically.
